

Jesid Mauricio Mejía Castro

Curriculum Vitae

Overview

Systems and Computer Engineer from the National University of Colombia. I am currently pursuing the title of Master in Engineering and Data Analytics from the Jorge Tadeo Lozano University. My experience covers databases and ETLs development in banking and financial services. I keep an obsessive spirit for learning and understanding complex subjects and I promote technical rigor and intense teamwork. I am deeply engaged with ethics in the workplace.

Personal Data

Address Cra. 13 C 165 - 86 Casa 35

Civil status Single

Birth date September 27, 1991

Phone +57 300 706 3656

Email jmauriciomejia@gmail.com

Education

Undergraduate degree

Ingeniero de Sistemas y Computación, Universidad Nacional de Colombia, Bogotá.

2012 - 2017

Graduate degree

UTADEO

Magíster en Ingeniería y Analítica de Datos, Universidad de Bogotá Jorge Tadeo Lozano,

2020 Bogotá.

(Ongoing)

Technical Skills

Advanced User

lopment

ETL Deve- IBM Infosphere DataStage

DBMS PL/SQL with Oracle Database. SQL with MS SQL Server 2012

Intermediate User

Programming Python, Java, VBA, R

Languages

Machine Regression, Classification, Clustering

Learning and Dimensionality Reduction

Languages

English High level of reading and listening

Job Experience

Years

2016 - 2017 Internship, Enel Codensa S.A. E.S.P..



In this utility company I completed my internship with the Customer Ombudsman Office. I was in charge of new developments and monthly reports (mainly with MS Access and VBA).

2018 - 2020 Analyst, Banco de Bogotá.



Between 2018 and 2019 I worked in the Credit Division developing in-house tools and database reports (with MS SQL Server 2012). Since mid 2019 until now I have been working in the Information Governance And Data Quality Office. I develop ETL projects and PL/SQL scripts aimed at measuring the quality for several data domains in the bank.